<ar>
2.19:
* تمت إضافة الدعم لاستيراد الملحوظات
* تم إصلاح خطأ كان يحدث عند البحث عن الملحوظات في أجهزة التابلت
* تمت إضافة حذف الحساب داخل التطبيق
* تم إصلاح شاشة التحقُّق من البريد الإلكتروني التي تظهر مع حسابات تم التحقُّق منها
*تم تغيير أيقونة الملحوظة الجديدة
</ar>
<de-DE>
2.19:
* Unterstützung zum Importieren von Notizen hinzugefügt
* Absturz beim Durchsuchen von Notizen auf Tablets behoben
* In-App-Kontolöschung hinzugefügt
* Anzeige des E-Mail-Verifizierungsbildschirms in verifizierten Konten behoben
* Icon für neue Notizen geändert
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
2.19:
* Se ha añadido compatibilidad para importar notas
* Se ha solucionado el bloqueo que se producía al buscar notas en tabletas
* Se ha añadido la función de eliminar la cuenta en la aplicación
* Se ha solucionado la pantalla de verificación del correo electrónico que aparecía para las cuentas verificadas
* Se ha cambiado el icono de nota nueva
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
2.19 :
* Ajout de la prise en charge pour importer des notes
* Résolution d’une défaillance lors de la recherche de notes sur tablettes
* Ajout de la suppression de compte dans l’application
* Correction de l’affichage de l’écran de vérification des e-mails avec des comptes vérifiés
* Modification de l’icône de nouvelle note
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
2.19:
* הוספנו תמיכה לייבוא פתקים
* תיקנו קריסה שהתרחשה כאשר מחפשים פתקים במכשירי טאבלט
* הוספנו אפשרות למחיקת חשבון באפליקציה
* תיקנו את המסך לאימות אימייל שמופיע בחשבונות מאומתים
* שינינו את הסמל של פתק חדש
</iw-IL>
<id>
2.19:
* Penambahan dukungan untuk mengimpor catatan
* Perbaikan kerusakan saat mencari catatan di tablet
* Penambahan penghapusan Akun di Dalam Aplikasi
* Perbaikan layar verifikasi email muncul dengan akun terverifikasi
* Perubahan gambar catatan baru
</id>
<it-IT>
2.19:
* Aggiunto supporto per importazione note
* Corretto arresto anomalo durante la ricerca delle note nei tablet
* Aggiunta eliminazione account in-app
* Corretta schermata di verifica e-mail che compare con gli account verificati
* Cambiata icona nuova nota
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
2.19:
* メモのインポートのサポートを追加
* タブレットでメモを検索する際に発生するクラッシュを修正
* アプリ内アカウントの削除を追加
* 検証済みアカウントが表示されるメール検証画面が開く問題を修正
* 新しいメモアイコンを変更
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
2.19:
* 메모 가져오기에 대한 지원 추가함
* 태블릿에서 메모 검색 시 충돌 수정함
* 앱 내 계정 삭제 추가함
* 확인한 계정이 표시되는 이메일 확인 화면을 수정함
* 새 메모 아이콘 변경함
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
2.19:
* Ondersteuning toegevoegd om notities te importeren
* Crash verholpen tijdens het zoeken van notities op tablets
* Accountverwijdering in de app toegevoegd
* E-mailverificatiescherm verschijnt bij geverifieerde accounts
* Het pictogram voor nieuwe notitie gewijzigd
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
2.19:
* Suporte adicionado para importar anotações
* Falha corrigida ao pesquisar anotações em tablets
* Exclusão de conta no aplicativo adicionada
* Exibição da tela de verificação de e-mail com contas verificadas corrigida
* Alteração do novo ícone de anotação
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
2.19:
* Добавлена поддержка импорта заметок.
* Исправлен сбой, возникавший при поиске заметок на планшетах.
* Добавлена поддержка удаления учётной записи в приложении.
* Экран подтверждения адреса электронной почты больше не появляется для подтверждённых учётных записей.
* Изменён новый значок заметок.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
2.19:
* Stöd för import av anteckningar har lagts till
* En krasch som uppstod vid sökning efter anteckningar på surfplattor har åtgärdats
* Kontoborttagning i appen har lagts till
* Skärmen för e-postverifiering har korrigerats och visas nu med verifierade konton
* Ikonen för ny anteckning har ändrats
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
2.19:
* Notları içe aktarmak için destek eklendi
* Tabletlerde not ararken oluşan kilitlenme durumu düzeltildi
* Uygulamada Hesap Silme özelliği eklendi
* Doğrulanmış hesaplarda artık sabit e-posta doğrulama ekranı görüntülenir
* Yeni not simgesi değiştirildi
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
2.19：
* 添加了对导入备注的支持
* 修复了在平板电脑中搜索备注时发生的崩溃
* 添加了应用程序内账户删除
* 修复了已验证的账户中显示的电子邮件验证屏幕
* 更改了新的备注图标
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
2.1：:
* 新增匯入備註支援
* 修復在平板電腦中搜尋備註時的當機情況
* 新增應用程式內刪除帳號功能
* 修復已驗證帳號顯示電子郵件驗證畫面的問題
* 變更新備註圖示
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
2.19:
* Added support to import notes
* Fixed crash when searching notes in tablets
* Added In App Account Deletion
* Fixed email verification screen appears with verified accounts
* Changed the new note icon
</en-US>
