<ar>
2.25:
جديد: Simplenote Sustainer. ساعد على دعم تطوير Simplenote المستمر مع أحد الاشتراكات السنوية.
</ar>
<de-DE>
2.25:
Neu: Simplenote-Unterstützer. Unterstütze mit einem Jahresabonnement die kontinuierliche Entwicklung von Simplenote.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
2.25:
Novedad: Contribuidor de Simplenote. Contribuye al desarrollo continuo de Simplenote con una suscripción anual.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
2.25 :
Nouveau : devenez contributeur de Simplenote. Soutenez le développement continu de Simplenote avec un abonnement annuel.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
2.25:
חדש: Simplenote Sustainer. אפשר לתמוך בפיתוח המתמשך של Simplenote דרך מינוי שנתי.
</iw-IL>
<id>
2.25:
Baru: Simplenote Sustainer. Bantu dukung pengembangan Simplenote yang sedang berlangsung dengan langganan tahunan.
</id>
<it-IT>
2.25:
Novità: sostenitore Simplenote. Aiuta a sostenere lo sviluppo continuo di Simplenote con un abbonamento annuale.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
2.25:
新着: Simplenote Sustainer 年間サブスクリプションで Simplenote の継続的な開発をサポートしてください。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
2.25:
신규: Simplenote 지지자. 연간 구독으로 Simplenote의 지속적인 개발에 도움이 되도록 지지해 주세요.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
2.25:
Nieuw: Simplenote Sustainer. Help de continue ontwikkeling van Simplenote ondersteunen met een jaarlijks abonnement.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
2.25:
Novidade: apoiador do Simplenote. Ajude a apoiar o desenvolvimento contínuo do Simplenote com uma assinatura anual.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
2.25:
Новинка: спонсор Simplenote. Оформите годовую подписку: этим вы сделаете весомый вклад в разработку приложения Simplenote.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
2.25:
Nyhet: Simplenote Sustainer. Hjälp till att stödja den pågående utvecklingen av Simplenote med en årlig prenumeration.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
2.25:
Yeni: Simplenote Sustainer. Yıllık abonelikle Simplenote'un sürekli olarak geliştirilmesini desteklemeye yardımcı olun.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
2.25：
新内容：Simplenote 支持者。 购买年度订阅，帮助支持 Simplenote 的持续开发。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
2.25：
新功能：Simplenote Sustainer。 以年約方案的方式，協助支持 Simplenote 持續開發。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
2.25:
New: Simplenote Sustainer. Help support the ongoing development of Simplenote with an annual subscription.
</en-US>
