<ar>
2.4:
* تم تحديث المعلومات الواردة في الملحوظات مع تاريخ التعديل وتاريخ الإنشاء وعدد الكلمات وعدد الأحرف.
* تم نقل بعض الخيارات الواردة في الملحوظات من المعلومات الواردة في الملحوظات وشريط الإجراءات إلى قائمة علامات القطع.
* تم إصلاح أخطاء المزامنة مع حذف الوسوم وإفراغ سلة المهملات.
* تم إصلاح أخطاء الشبكات التي تسببت في تباطؤ التطبيق.
</ar>
<de-DE>
2.4:
* Notizeninformationen mit Änderungsdatum, Erstellungsdatum, Wortanzahl und Zeichenanzahl aktualisiert.
* Einige Notizenoptionen aus den Notizeninformationen und der Aktionsleiste in das Dreipunkt-Menü verschoben.
* Einen Synchronisierungsfehler beim Löschen von Schlagwörtern und Leeren des Papierkorbs behoben.
* Einen Netzwerkfehler behoben, der zu Verzögerungen der App führte.
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
2.4:
* Información actualizada de las notas con la fecha de modificación, la fecha de creación, el número de palabras y el número de caracteres.
* Hemos trasladado algunas opciones de notas de la información de las notas y la barra de acción al menú de tres puntos.
* Hemos solucionado un error de sincronización que ocurría al eliminar etiquetas y vaciar la papelera.
* Hemos solucionado un error de red que hacía que la aplicación se retrasara.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
2.4 :
*Mise à jour des informations sur les notes de version incluant la date de modification, la date de création, le nombre de mots et le nombre de caractères.
*Déplacement de certaines options de notes de version des informations sur ces dernières et de la barre d'action vers le menu représenté par trois points.
*Résolution d'un bug de synchronisation avec suppression des étiquettes et vidage de la corbeille.
*Résolution d'un bug d'interconnexion réseau qui faisait ralentissait l'application.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
2.4:
* פרטים מעודכנים לפתקים, כולל תאריך שינוי, תאריך יצירה, ספירת מילים וספירת תווים.
* הזזנו כמה מאפשרויות הפתקים שבפרטי הפתק ובסרגל הפעולות לתפריט של שלוש הנקודות.
* תיקנו את באג הסנכרון שמחק תגיות ורוקן את הפח.
* מחקנו את באג הרשת שהאט את פעילות האפליקציה.
</iw-IL>
<id>
2.4:
* Informasi catatan diperbarui dengan tanggal diubah, tanggal dibuat, jumlah kata, dan jumlah karakter.
* Memindahkan beberapa pilihan catatan dari informasi catatan dan bilah tindakan ke menu elipsis.
* Memperbaiki bug dengan menghapus tag dan mengosongkan tempat sampah.
* Memperbaiki bug jaringan yang membuat aplikasi mengalami lag.
</id>
<it-IT>
2.4:
*Informazioni della nota aggiornate con data di modifica, data di creazione, conteggio parole e conteggio caratteri.
*Alcune opzioni della nota spostate dalle informazioni della nota e dalla barra delle azioni al menu ellissi.
*Risolto un bug relativo alla sincronizzazione con eliminazione di tag e svuotamento del cestino.
*Risolto un bug di rete che causava il ritardo dell'app.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
2.4:
* メモ情報の変更日、作成日、単語数、文字数を更新しました。
* 複数のメモオプションを、メモ情報とアクションバーから省略記号メニューに移動しました。
* タグを削除したときやゴミ箱を空にしたときに発生する同期のバグを修正しました。
* アプリの速度低下を引き起こしていたネットワーキングのバグを修正しました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
2.4:
* 수정된 날짜, 생성된 날짜, 단어 수 및 문자 수로 업데이트된 메모 정보.
* 일부 메모 옵션을 메모 정보 및 작업 표시줄에서 줄임표 메뉴로 옮겼습니다.
* 태그 삭제 및 휴지통 비우기와의 동기화 버그가 수정되었습니다.
* 앱이 지연되는 네트워킹 버그가 수정되었습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
2.4:
* Bijgewerkte notitiegegevens met aangepaste datum, aanmaakdatum, aantal woorden en aantal tekens.
* Aantal notitie-opties verplaatst van notitiegegevens en de actiebalk naar het ellipsmenu.
* Synchronisatieprobleem opgelost waarbij codes werden verwijderd en de prullenbak werd geleegd.
* Netwerkprobleem opgelost waardoor de app traag werd.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
2.4:
* Informações de nota atualizadas com data de modificação, data de criação, contagem de palavras e contagem de caracteres.
* Algumas opções de nota foram movidas das informações de nota e da barra de ações para o menu de elipse.
* Bug de sincronização com tags excluídas e lixeira vazia resolvido.
* Bug de serviço de rede que causava lentidão no aplicativo resolvido.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
Версия 2.4:
* Обновленная информация о заметках с указанием даты изменения, даты создания, количества слов и количества символов.
* Некоторые параметры заметок перенесены из раздела информации о заметках и панели действий в меню под знаком многоточия.
* Исправлена ошибка синхронизации с удалением тегов и очисткой корзины.
* Исправлена сетевая ошибка, из-за которой приложение зависало.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
2.4:
* Uppdaterad meddelandeinformation med datum ändrat, datum skapat, antal ord och antal tecken.
* Flyttade några meddelandealternativ från meddelandeinformationen och åtgärdsfältet till ellips-menyn.
* Åtgärdade en synkroniseringsbugg med att ta bort etiketter och tömma papperskorgen.
* Åtgärdade en nätverksbugg som fick appen att lagga.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
2.4:
* Not bilgisi; değiştirilme tarihi, oluşturulma tarihi, kelime sayısı ve karakter sayısı ile güncellendi.
* Not bilgisindeki bazı not seçenekleri ve eylem çubuğu, üç nokta menüsüne taşındı.
* Etiketleri silme ve çöpü boşaltma ile ilgili senkronizasyon hatası düzeltildi.
* Uygulamada gecikmeye neden olan bir ağ hatası düzeltildi.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
2.4：
* 更新了说明信息，包括修改日期、创建日期、字数和字符数。
* 将说明信息和操作栏中的一些说明选项移动到了省略号菜单中。
* 修复了删除标签和清空回收站的同步错误。
* 修复了导致应用程序延迟的网络错误。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
2.4：
* 更新修改日期、建立日期、字數和字元數的備註資訊。
* 將部分備註選項從備註資訊和動作列移至省略符號選單。
* 修正刪除標籤和清空垃圾桶時的同步錯誤。
* 修正造成應用程式延遲的網路錯誤。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
2.4:
* Updated note information with date modified, date created, word count, and character count.
* Moved some note options from note information and the action bar to the ellipsis menu.
* Fixed a syncing bug with deleting tags and emptying trash.
* Fixed a networking bug that made the app lag.
</en-US>
