<ar>
2.1:
* تم تحديث القالب المظلم باستخدام ألوان داكنة لتقليل إجهاد العينين وتحسين عمر البطارية.
* تم تحديث واجهة درج التنقل لتحسين التنظيم والتوافق.
* تم تنظيم واجهة قائمة الملحوظات لتحسين الأداء وقابلية القراءة.
* تمت إزالة إذن الوصول إلى الموقع للقالب المظلم في الليل فقط.
</ar>
<de-DE>
2.1:
* Dunkles Theme mit dunkleren Farben aktualisiert, damit Augen nicht so schnell ermüden und die Akkulaufzeit verbessert wird
* Menübereich zur Navigation aktualisiert, um Organisation und Kompatibilität zu verbessern
* Notizenliste aktualisiert, um Performance und Lesbarkeit zu verbessern
* Standortberechtigung für „Nur nachts dunkel“-Theme entfernt
</de-DE>
<es-ES>
2.1:
* Hemos actualizado el tema Oscuro con colores más oscuros para reducir la fatiga visual y el consumo de batería.
* Hemos actualizado la interfaz del cajón de navegación para mejorar la organización y la compatibilidad.
* Hemos actualizado la interfaz de la lista de notas para mejorar el rendimiento y la legibilidad.
* Hemos quitado el permiso de ubicación para el tema Oscuro solo de noche.
</es-ES>
<fr-FR>
2.1 :
* Mise à jour du thème sombre et ajout de couleurs plus sombres pour diminuer la fatigue oculaire et améliorer l'autonomie de la batterie.
* Mise à jour de l'interface du menu de navigation pour une meilleure organisation et une compatibilité accrue.
* Mise à jour de l'interface de la liste de notes pour améliorer les performances et la lisibilité.
* Suppression de l'autorisation concernant l'emplacement géographique pour le thème sombre la nuit uniquement.
</fr-FR>
<iw-IL>
2.1:
* ערכת עיצוב כהה מעודכנת עם צבעים כהים יותר כדי למנוע עייפות של העיניים וניצול סוללה.
* ממשק מעודכן בסרגל הניווט לארגון וההתאמה טובים יותר.
* ממשק מעודכן ברשימת הפתקים לביצועים משופרים ולקריאה נוחה יותר.
* הסרנו את הרשאות המיקום בערכת עיצוב שמשתנה לצבעים כהים בשעות הלילה בלבד.
</iw-IL>
<id>
2.1:
* Memperbarui tema gelap dengan warna yang lebih gelap agar mata tidak mudah lelah dan baterai lebih tahan lama.
* Memperbarui antarmuka drawer navigasi untuk organisasi dan kompatibilitas yang lebih baik.
* Memperbarui antarmuka daftar catatan untuk performa dan keterbacaan yang lebih baik.
* Menghapus izin lokasi untuk tema hanya gelap saat malam.
</id>
<it-IT>
2.1:
* Tema scuro aggiornato con colori più scuri per aumentare la durata della batteria e affaticare meno gli occhi.
* Interfaccia del menu di navigazione aggiornata per migliorare l'organizzazione e la compatibilità.
* Interfaccia dell'elenco delle note aggiornata per migliorare le prestazioni e la leggibilità.
* Autorizzazione della posizione rimossa per il tema scuro solo di notte.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
2.1:
* 目が疲れにくくバッテリーが長持ちする、より暗い色にダークテーマを更新しました。
* より整理しやすく互換性が広がるようにナビゲーションドロワーインターフェースを更新しました。
* パフォーマンスが向上し、見やすくなるようにメモリストインターフェースを更新しました。
* 色の暗い夜間専用のテーマに必要な位置情報の許可を削除しました。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
2.1:
* 눈의 피로를 줄이고 배터리 수명을 연장하기 위해 더 어두운 색상으로 어두운 테마를 업데이트했습니다.
* 구성 및 호환성을 개선하기 위해 탐색 보관함 인터페이스를 업데이트했습니다.
* 성능과 가독성을 개선하기 위해 메모 목록 인터페이스를 업데이트했습니다.
* 야간 전용 테마에 대한 위치 권한을 제거했습니다.
</ko-KR>
<nl-NL>
2.1:
* Donker thema bijgewerkt met donkerdere kleuren om vermoeidheid van de ogen te verminderen en de levensduur van de batterij te verbeteren.
* Interface van het navigatiemenu bijgewerkt voor verbeterde ordening en compatibiliteit.
* Interface van de notitielijst bijgewerkt voor verbeterde prestaties en leesbaarheid.
* Locatiemachtiging verwijderd van 'alleen 's nachts donker' thema.
</nl-NL>
<pt-BR>
2.1:
* Tema noturno atualizado com cores mais escuras para vista menos cansada e maior duração da bateria.
* Interface de gaveta de navegação atualizada para melhor organização e compatibilidade.
* Interface de lista de anotações atualizada para melhor desempenho e leitura.
* Permissão de localização removida para o tema noturno somente à noite.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
Версия 2.1
* Обновленная тёмная тема с более насыщенными цветами снижает нагрузку на глаза и увеличивает срок службы батареи.
* Обновленный интерфейс панели навигации упорядочивает представление элементов и повышает совместимость.
* Обновленный интерфейс списка заметок увеличивает эффективность и удобство чтения.
* Удалено требование разрешения на доступ к сведениям о местоположении для темы, которая становится тёмной только в ночное время.
</ru-RU>
<sv-SE>
2.1:
* Det mörka temat har uppdaterats med mörkare färger för mindre ögontrötthet och bättre batteritid.
* Gränssnittet för navigeringsreglaget har uppdaterats för bättre organisering och kompatibilitet.
* Gränssnittet för anteckningslistan har uppdaterats för bättre prestanda och läsbarhet.
* Platsbehörigheten för mörkt-på-natten-temat har tagits bort.
</sv-SE>
<tr-TR>
2.1:
* Göz yorgunluğunu azaltmak ve daha iyi pil ömrü sağlamak için koyu renk teması daha koyu renklerle güncellendi.
* Daha iyi düzen ve uyumluluk için gezinme çizici arayüzü güncellendi.
* Daha iyi performans ve okunabilirlik için not listesi arayüzü güncellendi.
* Yalnızca geceleyin koyu temasında konum izni kaldırıldı.
</tr-TR>
<zh-CN>
2.1：
* 使用较暗的颜色更新了深色主题，可缓解眼睛疲劳，延长电池续航时间。
* 更新了导航抽屉界面，使之更有条理、更具兼容性。
* 更新了注释列表界面，使之实现更好的性能、更加清晰易读。
* 删除了仅限夜间主题的位置权限。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
2.1：
* 更新深色佈景主題，增加一些深色選擇，以減少眼睛疲勞、延長電池壽命。
* 更新導覽抽屜介面，新的介面將更有組織，相容性也更高。
* 更新備註清單介面，使用效能提升，讀起來更為方便。
* 移除「只有夜晚變成深色」(dark at night only) 佈景主題的位置權限。
</zh-TW>
<en-US>
2.1:
* Updated dark theme with darker colors for less eye fatigue and better battery life.
* Updated navigation drawer interface for better organization and compatibility.
* Updated note list interface for better performance and readability.
* Removed location permission for dark at night only theme.
/<en-US>
